ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Workers' Rights- OSHA, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  WNYCOSH, #4145, 2/2/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  K. Stewart, #4147, 1/20/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  Dr. Madhurika, #4148, 1/20/12
- Indoor Environment Quality, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  GHHI, #4149, 3/19-20/12
- Indoor Environment Quality, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  GHHI, #4150, 4/2-3/12
- Indoor Environment Quality, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  GHHI, #4151, 5/7-8/12
- Indoor Environment Quality, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  GHHI, #4152, 7/16, 23/12
- Indoor Environment Quality, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  GHHI, #4153, 8/1-2/12
- Indoor Environment Quality, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  GHHI, #4154, 9/17-18/12
- Indoor Environment Quality, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  GHHI, #4155, 10/1-2/12
- Indoor Environment Quality, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  GHHI, #4156, 10/11-12/12
- Indoor Environment Quality, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  GHHI, #4157, 11/1-2/12
- Conference Module, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 55)
  USCC, #4158, 1/29/13
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 35, Folder 56)
  Building Science, #4159, 1/23/12
- Tech. Asst., 2011 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  Gillette Cons., #4160, 12/1/11
- Spring Tech. Conference, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 58)
  NYWEA, #4161, 6/6/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 35, Folder 59)
  Cope and Assoc., #4162, 2/3/12
- #4163 (Proposed), 2012 (Box 35, Folder 60)
- Infection Control (Proposed), 2012 (Box 35, Folder 61)
  WNYCOSH, #4164, 5/14/12
- Interview, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 62)
  National Geographic/Taboo, #4165, 2/28/12
- MCWA Seasonal Workers, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 63)
  WNYCOSH, #4166, 5/24/13
- MCWA Seasonal Workers, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 64)
  WNYCOSH, #4167, 6/19/13
- NFWB- Biohazards, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 65)
  WNYCOSH, #4168, 5/1/13
- NFWB- Biohazards, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 66)
  WNYCOSH, #4169, 5/2/13
- Sleep Deprivation, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 67)
  NYSDOT, #4170, 11/7/12
- NYSTA, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 68)
  WNYCOSH, #4171, 5/1/12
- Vulnerable Workers, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 69)
  WNYCOSH, #4172, 9/19/12
- Vulnerable Workers, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 70)
  WNYCOSH, #4173, 9/20/12
- Vulnerable Workers, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 71)
  WNYCOSH, #4174, 9/20/12
- Vulnerable Workers, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 72)
  WNYCOSH, #4175, 9/25/12
- Vulnerable Workers, 2011-2012 (Box 35, Folder 73)
  WNYCOSH- OSHA
- GHHI- Trainer, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 74)
  Coalition to End Childhood Pb (Lead) Poisoning, #4176, 3/26-27/12
- Reviewer- Curriculum on Aging, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 75)
  CDMS, #4177, 7/25/12
- Composting Health and Safety, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 76)
  WNYCOSH, #4179, 4/14/12
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 77)
  Public- Rochester Literacy, 11C#4178, 6/4/12, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 78)
  #4180, 1/14/13, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 79)
  #4181, 1/24/13, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 80)
  #4182, 2/5/13, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 81)
  #4183, 2/25/13, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  #4184, 3/8/13, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator Initial, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  #4185, 3/21/13, Wheaton
- Bureau Veritas- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, #4186, 7/17/12
- Bureau Veritas- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, #4187, 7/17/12
- Bureau Veritas- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  WNYCOSH, #4188, 7/17/12
- Bureau Veritas- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, #4189, 7/17/12
- Bureau Veritas- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, #4190, 7/18/12
- MCWA, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, #4191, 5/22/12
- MCWA, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, #4192, 5/31/12
- NFWB- Hazop, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  WNYCOSH, #4193, 5/9/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  M. Dodson, esq., #4194, 3/28/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  Covanta Energy, #4195, 3/29/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  W. Seneca Schools, #4196, 3/30/12
- Farm Digester, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  WNYCOSH, #4197, 7/28/12
- Green Cleaning, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  WNY Environmental Summit, #4199, 9/29/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  Federal Mediation Service, #4200, 2/13/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  Erie I Boces, #4201, 3/9/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  Snyder Industries, #4202, 3/22/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  V. Innis, #4204, 3/16/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  Seed and Cycle, #4205, 4/16/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  Diernisse, #4206, 4/13/12
- Review Article, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  Polish J. of Environmental Studies, #4207, 4/16/12
- Safe Resident Handling- Team Skills, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH, #4208, 4/11/13
- Blood Borne Pathogens- It Takes a Village, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  WNYCOSH, #4209, 5/9/12
- Airborne Diseases- It Takes a Village, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  WNYCOSH, #4210, 5/17/12
- Green Cleaning- It Takes a Village, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, #4211, 5/21/12
- Cleaning and Disinfecting Chemicals- It Takes a Village, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH, #4212, 6/1/12
- Tech. Asst.- Student, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  Cornell ILR, #4213, 4/23/12
- Esse- Env. (Proposed), 2012 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  #4214
- Confined Space- NFWB, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  WNYCOSH, #4215, 6/26/12
- LRRP-I, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  Community Foundation, #4216, 5/29/12
- No. 4217: Green and Healthy Homes Initiative (GHHI) Lead Renovator [Folder 1 of 2], 2012 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- No. 4217: Green and Healthy Homes Initiative (GHHI) Lead Renovator [Folder 2 of 2], 2012 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- LRRP-I, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  Community FNDN, #4217, 6/11/12
- Tech. Asst., 2013 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  Hilton S.D., #4218, 1/9/13
- MCWA- Hazcom- Office, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  WNYCOSH, #4219, 5/31/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  M. DaSilva, #4220, 5/16/12
- Orangetown WWTP, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  WNYCOSH, #4221, 6/21/12
- Albany WWTP, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  WNYCOSH, #4222, 7/31/12
- Aging Workforce- Interview, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  CDMS, #4224, 6/5/12
- Town of Amherst WWTP- Biohazards and Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  WNYCOSH, #4225, 7/26/12
- Town of Amherst WWTP- Biohazards and Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  WNYCOSH, #4226, 7/26/12
- City of Buffalo- Violence, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  WNYCOSH, #4227, 7/19/12
- City of Buffalo- Violence, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  WNYCOSH, #4228, 7/19/12
- City of Buffalo- Violence, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  WNYCOSH, #4229, 7/20/12
- City of Buffalo- Violence, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  WNYCOSH, #4230, 7/20/12
- City of Buffalo- Violence, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  WNYCOSH, #4231, 7/27/12
- City of Buffalo- Violence, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  WNYCOSH, #4232, 7/25/12
- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  WNYCOSH, #4233, 8/7/12
- Airborne Pathogens, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  WNYCOSH, #4234, 8/8/12
- Green Cleaning, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  WNYCOSH, #4235, 8/9/12
- Disinfectants, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  WNYCOSH, #4236, 8/13/12
- Sleep Deprivation, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 53)
  NYSDOT, #4237, 11/7/12
- City of Buffalo- Violence, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 54)
  WNYCOSH, #4238, 8/7/12
- City of Buffalo- Violence, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 55)
  WNYCOSH, #4239, 8/8/12
- City of Buffalo- Violence, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 56)
  WNYCOSH, #4240, 8/13/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 57)
  WNYCOSH, #4257, 8/14/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 58)
  WNYCOSH, #4258, 6/8/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 59)
  WNYCOSH, #4259, 6/8/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 60)
  WNYCOSH, #4260, 6/18/12
- Confined Space- NYWEA, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 61)
  WNYCOSH, #4261, 4/8/13
- Crisis Management, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 62)
  WNYCOSH, #4262, 6/17/13
- Crisis Management, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 63)
  WNYCOSH, #4263, 3/5/13
- Crisis Management, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 64)
  WNYCOSH, #4264, 3/6/13
- NYWEA, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 65)
  WNYCOSH, #4265, 7/11/12
- NYWEA, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 66)
  WNYCOSH, #4266, 7/9/13
- WNYCOSH (Proposed), 2012 (Box 36, Folder 67)
  #4267
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 68)
  B. Hollis, #4268, 8/14/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 69)
  J. Bertolou, Dvm., #4269, 8/15/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 70)
  D. Gaskill, #4270, 8/20/12
- Vulnerable Workers, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 71)
  WNYCOSH, #4271, 9/25/12
- Vulnerable Workers- Journey's End, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 72)
  WNYCOSH, #4272, 9/24/12
- Conference Module, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 73)
  NYWEA, #4273, 2/5/13
- Kaleida- Buffalo General Medical Center, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 74)
  WNYCOSH, #4274, 11/29/12
- Kaleida- Flint Rd., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 75)
  WNYCOSH, #4275, 11/26/12
- Kaleida- DeGraff, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 76)
  WNYCOSH, #4276, 12/12/12
- Kaleida- VNA, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 77)
  WNYCOSH, #4277, 12/12/12
- Kaleida- Women's and Children's Hospital, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 78)
  WNYCOSH, #4278, 12/13/12
- Art Safety and Health, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 79)
  WNYCOSH, #4279, 4/19/13
- JHA- Try It, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 80)
  WNYCOSH, #4280, 2/20/13
- Safety and Health Committee Skills- Try It, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 81)
  WNYCOSH, #4281, 3/13/13
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 82)
  Bureau Veritas, #4286, 9/6/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 36, Folder 83)
  WNYCOSH, #4287, 12/13/12
- Buffalo Schools (Proposed), 2012 (Box 36, Folder 84)
  WNYCOSH, #4288, 12/5/12
- Buffalo Schools- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 85)
  WNYCOSH, #4289, 4/4/13
- Clean Air Coalition- Firefighters and Breast Cancer (Proposed), 2012 (Box 36, Folder 86)
  WNYCOSH, #4290, 12/13/12
- Erie County- Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 87)
  WNYCOSH, #4291, 1/31/13
- Erie County- Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 88)
  WNYCOSH, #4292, 2/1/13
- Erie County DSS- Ergonomics/Computers, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 89)
  WNYCOSH, #4293, 5/2/13
- Erie County- Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 90)
  WNYCOSH, #4295, 3/19/13
- Erie County- Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 91)
  WNYCOSH, #4296, 3/20/13
- Erie County- Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 92)
  WNYCOSH, #4297, 3/21/13
- Erie County- Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 93)
  WNYCOSH, #4298, 4/23/13
- Erie County- Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 36, Folder 94)
  WNYCOSH, #4300, 5/14/13
- Confined Space- Lewistown WWTP, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 95)
  WNYCOSH, #4301, 11/6/12
- Hazcom/GHS- Lewistown WWTP, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 96)
  WNYCOSH, #4302, 11/13/12
- High Pressure Injection Injuries- Lewistown WWTP, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 97)
  WNYCOSH, #4303, 11/27/12
- Buffalo Schools, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 98)
  WNYCOSH, #4304, 10/15/12
- Buffalo Schools, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 99)
  WNYCOSH, #4305, 10/16/12
- Buffalo Schools, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 100)
  WNYCOSH, #4306, 10/17/12
- Buffalo Schools, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 101)
  WNYCOSH, #4307, 10/17/12
- Buffalo Schools, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 102)
  WNYCOSH, #4308, 10/18/12
- Buffalo Schools, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, #4309, 10/18/12
- Buffalo Schools, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  WNCOSH, #4310, 10/19/12
- Buffalo Schools, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, #4311, 10/22/12
- Buffalo Schools, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, #4312, 10/23/12
- Buffalo Schools, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  WNYCOSH, #4313, 10/23/12
- Buffalo Schools, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, #4314, 10/24/12
- Buffalo Schools, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, #4315, 10/26/12
- Erie County WWTP- Stress, Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, #4316, 1/8/13
- Erie County WWTP- Stress, Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, #4317, 1/8/13
- Erie County WWTP- Stress, Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  WNYCOSH, #4318, 1/16/13
- Erie County WWTP- Stress, Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  WNYCOSH, #4319, 1/16/13
- Erie County WWTP- Stress, Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  WNYCOSH, #4320, 1/24/13
- Erie County WWTP- Stress, Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH, #4321, 1/24/13
- Erie County WWTP- Fundamentals of Chemical Exposure, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  WNYCOSH, #4322, 3/14/13
- Erie County WWTP- Interest Based Problem Solving- Health and Safety, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH, #4323, 4/17/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence- R, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  WNYCOSH, #4324, 11/30/12
- Niagara Falls- Violence- R, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, #4325, 11/30/12
- Niagara Falls- Violence- R, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, #4326, 12/3/12
- Niagara Falls- Violence- R, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  WNYCOSH, #4327, 12/3/12
- Niagara Falls- Violence- R, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  WNYCOSH, #4328, 12/4/12
- Niagara Falls- Violence- R, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, #4329, 12/4/12
- Niagara Falls- Violence- R, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH, #4330, 12/6/12
- Niagara Falls- Violence- R, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH, #4331, 12/6/12
- Hazmat- I (Constantia), 2013 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  IUOE, #4332, 1/15/13
- Hazmat- I (Dansville), 2013 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  IUOE, #4333, 2/12/13
- Disaster Site Worker (Dansville), 2013 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  IUOE, #4334, 2/18/13
- Niagara Falls- Water Board- Violence- R, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH, #4335, 10/29/12
- Niagara Falls- Water Board- Violence- R, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  WNYCOSH, #4336, 10/29/12
- Niagara Falls- Water Board- Violence- R, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  WNYCOSH, #4337, 11/5/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  Cornell Worker Institute, #4338, 9/19/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  Water Research Commission, South Africa, #4339, 9/14/12
- Erie County- Accident Investigation, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  WNYCOSH, #4340, 10/22/12
- Erie County- Committee Skills, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  WNYCOSH, #4341, 10/24/12
- Erie County- Crisis Management, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  WNYCOSH, #4342, 4/16/13
- Erie County- Stress, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  WNYCOSH, #4343, 4/16/13
- Erie County- Crisis Management, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  WNYCOSH, #4344, 4/18/13
- Erie County- Stress, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, #4345, 4/18/13
- Elmira Water Board- Violence, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  WNYCOSH, #4346, 11/14/12
- Elmira Water Board- Violence, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  WNYCOSH, #4347, 11/14/12
- Elmira Water Board- Violence, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  WNYCOSH, #4348, 11/14/12
- Elmira Water Board- Violence, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  WNYCOSH, #4349, 11/14/12
- Green Cleaning, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  ZONTA, #4350, 10/16/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  N. Graham, #4351, 9/14/12
- Tech. Asst., 2012 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  A. Rosen, #4352, 9/12/12
- Hazmat- R, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  IUOE, #4353, 2/13/13
- Hazmat- R, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  IUOE, #4354, 2/14/13
- Hazmat- R, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  IUOE, #4355, 2/15/13
- Hazmat- R, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  IUOE, #4356, 2/19/13
- Hazmat- R, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  IUOE, #4357, 2/25/13
- Xylem- PPE, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  WNYCOSH, #4358, 11/28/12
- Xylem- PPE, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  WNYCOSH, #4359, 11/28/12
- Xylem- PPE, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  WNYCOSH, #4360, 11/28/12
- Xylem- PPE, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  WNYCOSH, #4361, 11/28/12
- Xylem- Hazcom/GHS, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  WNYCOSH, #4362, 6/11/13
- Xylem- Hazcom/GHS, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  WNYCOSH, #4363, 6/11/13
- Xylem- Hazcom/GHS, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 56)
  WNYCOSH, #4364, 6/11/13
- Xylem- Hazcom/GHS, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  WNYCOSH, #4365, 6/11/13
- Work/Health/Health Care, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 58)
  Cornell Resident, #4366, 2/26/13
- Green Cleaning, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  Women's Society of Unitarian/Universalist Church, #4367, 11/15/12
- Lewiston WWTP, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  WNYCOSH, #4368, 12/11/12
- Lewiston WWTP, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  WNYCOSH, #4369, 12/18/12
- Vulnerable Workers- Lead and Asbestos, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 62)
  WNYCOSH, #4370, 11/12/12
- Vulnerable Workers- Stress/Shiftwork, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 63)
  WNYCOSH, #4371, 11/13/13
- Vulnerable Workers- Thermal Stress, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 64)
  WNYCOSH, #4372, 11/15/12
- Kaleida- Millard Fillmore Suburban Hospital, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 65)
  WNYCOSH, #4373, 12/14/12
- Kaleida- HighPointe, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 66)
  WNYCOSH, #4374, 12/17/12
- Interview, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 67)
  LED Magazine, #4375, 11/12/12
- #4376, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 68)
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 69)
  WNYCOSH, #4376, 12/4/12
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 70)
  WNYCOSH, #4377, 12/4/12
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 71)
  WNYCOSH, #4378, 12/6/12
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 72)
  WNYCOSH, #4379, 12/13/12
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 73)
  WNYCOSH, #4380, 12/17/12
- GBEC Conference, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 74)
  WNYCOSH, #4381, 3/26/13
- Marycatt- Violence Tipsheet, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 75)
  #4382, 12/19/12
- Bureau Veritas- Computer Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 76)
  WNYCOSH, #4384, 2/21/13
- Bureau Veritas- Blood Borne Pathogens- Compliance, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 77)
  WNYCOSH, #4386, 2/22/13
- Bureau Veritas- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 78)
  WNYCOSH, #4388, 3811/13
- Bureau Veritas- Computer Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 79)
  WNYCOSH, #4389, 3/11/13
- Bureau Veritas- Hazcom/GHS, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 80)
  WNYCOSH, #4390, 3/11/13
- Bureau Veritas- Lab Standard, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 81)
  WNYCOSH, #4391, 3/12/13
- Bureau Veritas- Computer Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 82)
  WNYCOSH, #4392, 3/12/13
- Bureau Veritas- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 83)
  WNYCOSH, #4393, 4/29/13
- Bureau Veritas- Hazcom/GHS, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 84)
  WNYCOSH, #4394, 4/29/13
- Erie County- Office Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 85)
  WNYCOSH, #4395, 1/18/13
- Occupational Chemical Exposure, 2012 (Box 37, Folder 86)
  WNYCOSH, #4397, 12/13/12
- NYSDOL HAB, 2011-2012 (Box 37, Folder 87)
- KC Wagner/DWV Nanny Certificate, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 88)
  Cornell ILR, #4298-4299
- Journey's End- Custodial Hazards, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 89)
  WNYCOSH, #4399, 2/6/13
- Interview, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 90)
  Talent Management Magazine, #4400, 1/23/13
- Mold Training, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 91)
  Comm. FNDN, #4401
- Bureau Veritas- Lab Standard, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 92)
  WNYCOSH, #4402, 4/30/13
- Workers' Rights, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 93)
  WNYCOSH, #4404, 2/11/13
- Hazcom/GS, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 94)
  WNYCOSH, #4405, 2/13/13
- Thermal Stress and Asbestos Awareness, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 95)
  WNYCOSH, #4406, 2/25/13
- Buffalo Schools- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 96)
  WNYCOSH, #4407, 4/4/13
- Confined Space, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 97)
  WNYCOSH, #4408, 2/27/13
- Personal Protective Equipment, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 98)
  WNYCOSH, #4409, 3/25/13
- Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 99)
  WNYCOSH, #4410, 3/27/13
- Buffalo Cosmetics Association, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 100)
  WNYCOSH, #4411, 3/25/13
- Workers' Rights- OSHA, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 101)
  WNYCOSH, #4413, 3/1/13
- Workplace Violence, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 102)
  WNYCOSH, #4414, 3/21/13
- Custodial Hazards, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 103)
  WNYCOSH, #4415, 3/22/13
- Mold, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 104)
  Comm. FNDN, #4416, 3/29/13
- GHHI, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 105)
  Comm. FNDN #4417, 4/1-2/13
- Mold, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 106)
  Comm. FNDN, #4418, 4/22/13
- Mold, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 107)
  Comm. FNDN, #4419, 7/7/13
- Mold, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 108)
  Comm. FNDN, #4420, 5/6/13
- GHHI, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 109)
  Comm. FNDN, #4421, 5/7-8/13
- Mold, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 110)
  Comm. FNDN, #4422, 6/4/13
- Art Hazards, 2013 (Box 37, Folder 111)
  WNYCOSH, #4423, 5/16/13
- Lead Hazards Awareness, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, #4424, 2/28/13
- Tech. Asst., 2013 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  Buffalo Schools, #4425, 2/15/13
- Tech. Asst.- Silica, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  Smart Sign, #4426, 2/22/13
- Confined Space- Agriculture, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, #4427, 6/21/13
- City Harvest (Proposed), 2013 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  #4428
- Art Hazards, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, #4429, 5/31/14
- Buffalo Schools- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, #4430, 4/5/13
- Buffalo Schools- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, #4431, 4/5/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, #4432, 5/31/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  WNCOSH, #4433, 5/31/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  WNYCOSH, #4434, 5/31/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  WNYCOSH, #4435, 5/31/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH, #4436, 5/28/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  WNYCOSH, #4437, 5/28/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH, #4438, 5/28/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  WNYCOSH, #4439, 5/28/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, #4440, 5/30/13
- NYSDOL HAB, 2012-2013 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  IUOE
- NYSDOL HAB, 2012-2013 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  WNYCOSH, #4441, 5/30/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, #4442, 5/30/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH, #4444, 6/3/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH, #4445, 6/3/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  WNYCOSH, #4446, 6/3/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  WNYCOSH, #4447, 6/3/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, #4448, 6/5/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH, #4449, 6/5/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  WNYCOSH, #4450, 6/5/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  WNYCOSH, #4451, 6/5/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  WNYCOSH, #4452, 6/6/13
- Buffalo School District- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  WNYCOSH, #4453, 6/6/13
- Safety and Health Committee Skills- Try It, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  WNYCOSH, #4456, 7/18/13
- Onondaga County- Respiratory Protection, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  WNYCOSH, #4457, 6/26/13
- Onondaga County- Respiratory Protection, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  WNYCOSH, #4458, 7/17/13
- Onondaga County- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  WNYCOSH, #4459, 6/26/13
- Onondaga County- Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  WNYCOSH, #4460, 7/17/13
- Onondaga County- Confined Space, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, #4461, 6/25/13
- Onondaga County- Confined Space, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  WNYCOSH, #4462, 7/16/13
- Onondaga County- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  WNYCOSH, #4463, 6/27/13
- Onondaga County- Blood Borne Pathogens, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  WNYCOSH, #4464, 6/27/13
- NYWEA- Endocrine Disruptors, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  WNYCOSH, #4465, 6/25/13
- Vulnerable Workers- Onondaga County (Proposed), 2013 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  WNYCOSH, #4466
- Chautauqua Utility District- Confined Space, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  WNYCOSH, #4468, 5/9/13
- MCWA- PPE/Resp/Hazcom/Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  WNYCOSH, #4470, 7/19/13
- MCWA- PPE/Resp/Hazcom/Noise, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  WNYCOSH, #4471, 7/31/13
- LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  Public, #4472, 5/7/13
- LRRP- I (Proposed), 2013 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  Chautauqua County, #4475
- Conference Module, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  USCC, #4476, 1/27-29/14
- NYWEA and APWA- Asphalt, Confined Space, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  WNYCOSH, #4478, 5/23/13
- Tip Sheet, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  Cornell ILR, #4479, 4/25/13
- Endocrine Disruptors, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 51)